Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box: 14, Folder: 6 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 44: AMTRAK Press Release re. First International Train, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 45: Fact Sheet on Mr. and Mrs. Richard Coniglio, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 46: AMTRAK Press Release re. 3-millionth passenger, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 47: AMTRAK New Name for National Railroad Passenger Corp., Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 48: Congress of Railway Unions Letter to Call Chief Executives, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    By D. Beattie. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Proposed Run of the Inaugural Trains, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 50: Transpo News Vol. 1 No. 6, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 51: News from National Assoc. of Railroad Passengers re. Rail Passenger Group Supports More Funds for Amtrak, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 52: Fact Feet re. National Railroad Passenger Corp (AMTRAK), Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    By Harriett Pitt and Harry Klemfuss. Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Statement before Subcomt. On Surface Transportation, Comt. On Commerce, U.S. Senate, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    By Anthony Haswell. Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Department of Transportation Press Release re. Metropark Dedication, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 55: AMTRAK Flyer, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 56: NRPC Pass Policy, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 57: National Railroad Passenger Corp. Memo re. Policy and Procedure; Passes, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Box: 14, Folder: 7 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Employee Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: History and Description, Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: A Joint Statement on 'Plan for Progress', Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Seventy Years of Serving America's Bounty, Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Education Assistance Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Handbook for Selectors, Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Box: 14, Folder: 8 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Great Falls Department, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Employees' Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Letter to Miss S. Harper re. Request for Information on Employee Programs, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    By William R. Baker. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Communications Manual, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: You and Anaconda, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Our New Benefit Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: The Need for Anaconda Grassroots Support on Public Affairs Issues, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Anaconda Concerned Citizens, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Your Career at Anaconda, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Performance Rating, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Information for Employees, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Insurance and Compensation Laws, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    By C.F. Kelley. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: Stockholder Information, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: Reduction Works, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Box: 14, Folder: 9 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Report on the Second Session, Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Box: 14, Folder: 10 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Employees' Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Box: 14, Folder: 11 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Look who will be your next door neighbors because of the McCarran Immigration Law, Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: What you should know about the McCarran Immigration Act, Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Box: 14, Folder: 12 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: APRI News Release, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
    By Bayard Rustin. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 13 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: On the Job, Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Box: 14, Folder: 14 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Ras Tanura Refinery - Arabic Language, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: The Arabian Sun, Vol. 34 No. 12, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Highlights of Your Benefits Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Living in Aramco Communities, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: ARAMCO World Magazine; Vol. 28 No. 1, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Box: 14, Folder: 15 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The World's Work, Publication (Box 14, Folder 15)
    By F. Burnham McLeary. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 16 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: General Safety Instructions, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Contributory Retirement Income Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: ARMCO Policies, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Retirement Income Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: National Supply Company, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: What's it really like?, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Steel, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: Non-Contributory Pension Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Box: 14, Folder: 17 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention Fundamentals & Industrial Hygiene, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
    By M.U. Eninger. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 18 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Containing Facts about the Business and Organization, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Phoenix Headquarters Group Medical and Hospitalization Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Salaried Employees Pension Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Welcome to Armour - 2 Copies, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Handbook for Greyond/Armour Employees at Greyhound Tower, Phoenix, AZ, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Your Own Directions: A Plan for Yourself, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Armour; Vol. 19 No. 1, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Phoenix Newsletter 139-142, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: The Armour Star; Vol. 1 No. 4, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 10: Employment and Service Record, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 11: Employees' Hospital and Surgical Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 12: Long Term Disability Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 13: Opportunities in Armour Research, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 14: Major Hospital and Medical Expense Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 15: Armour and Company Employees' Pension Fund Rules and Regulations, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 16: Prevent; Vol. 3 No. 3, 4 and Vol. 4 No. 1, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 17: Career Paths at Armour Foods, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 18: Engineering Management Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 19: Management Incentive Comt., Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 20: Go Greyhound; Vol. 12 No. 2, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 21: Report to Automation Fund Comt on Retraining and Placement Experience of Workers, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
    By Easton H. Conant. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, Folder: 19 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Employees' Supplemental Pension Fund, Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Letter to All Armour Credit Unions re. Operations as of May 1941, Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Selling and Merchandising, Manual on Lard and Shortening, Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Progress Report to Automation Comt., Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Your Job at Armour, Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: The Armour Star; Vol. 38 No. 3, Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: The Armour Production Story, Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: Opportunities in Armour Research, Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Item 9: Employee Pension Fund - Rules and Regulation, Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Item 10: Employee Supplemental Pension Fund, Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Box: 14, Folder: 20 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Labor Relations Program for Armour Management, Publication (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Box: 14, Folder: 21 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Intercom, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Management Commentary, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Personnel Performance and Development Review, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Careers, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: Disability Income Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: Retirement Income Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: Medical Care Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: Scholarship Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: Group Insurance Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 10: Workmen's Compensation Benefit, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 11: The Citizen's Stake in the Labor Union Problem, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
    By H.W. Prentis, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Safety Manual, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 13: Mobile Equipment Operations Handbook, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 14: Long Term Disability Income Protection Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 15: Dental Assistance Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 16: The Lancaster Digest; Vol 2 Issue 9, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 17: Group Insurance Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 18: Supplementary Material re. Summary Plan Descriptions of your Employee Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 19: Travel Accident Insurance, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 20: Partners in Business - for Stockholders, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 21: The Reporter, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 22: Production Management Course, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 23: Announcement of Employees' Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 24: Announcement of Employees' Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 25: General Retirement Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 26: Educational Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 27: Power Plant Training Course, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Box: 14, Folder: 22 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Citizen's Stake in the Labor Union Problem - 3 Copies, Publication (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: The Task of the Labor-Management Conference, Publication (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Government's Place in Post-War Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: Power Plant Training Course, Publication (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: Plant Fire Brigade Training, Publication (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Item 6: The Supervisory Six, Publication (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Item 7: Letter to Employees re. Communism Film, Publication (Box 14, Folder 22)
    By C.J. Backstrand. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Human Relations in Supervision, Publication (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Box: 14, Folder: 23 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Suggestions for Progress Form, Publication (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Suggestion Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Box: 14, Folder: 24 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Job Classification Sheet, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Wage Incentives, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Job Classification Procedure, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Box: 15, Folder: 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: What is the Merit Shop?, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: ABC Stands Up to Union Monopoly, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Landmarks in Construction Labor Law, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: What ABC Stands for, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Construction Safety Guide, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Motor Grader, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Life Insurance, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Do you know it's illegal, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Blue Print for Growth, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: $100,000 of Accidental 3D Insurance, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Careers in Construction, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Just what is the Merit Shop?, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: ABC'S Retirement Program, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Construction Methods and Equipment, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Hard Hat Unions Fight Back - Washington Post, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By Helen Dewar. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Info on OSHA Citations, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Security Plans, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Box: 15, Folder: 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: 35 Years of Protection, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Box: 15, Folder: 3 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Annual Message, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    By Samuel N. Samuels. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Annual Message, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Annual Message, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Fur Trade Review, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Box: 15, Folder: 4 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A Constitution of Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Construction - A Man's Work, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Wage Scales for the Basic Trades, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Wage Scales for the Basic Trades, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Agreement between District Councils of Local Unions of the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America and Labor Relations of Division of AGCA - NYS, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Industrial and General Pipefitting Agreement, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: How to Improve Collective Bargaining in Construction, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Industrial Relations Bulletin re. Labor Increases, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Southern California Subsistence Areas - 2 Copies, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Career Opportunities for Men and Women in Construction, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Organization and Work of the AGC, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Construction: Opportunities Unlimited - 4 Copies, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: If you are nervous that you may, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Civil Defense- Emergency Organization, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Careers in Construction, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Occupational Summary: Iron Workers - 2 Copies, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Occupational Summary: Cement Masons, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Occupational Summary: Operating Engineer, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Occupational Summary: Bricklayers, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Firm List, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Letter explaining role of AGC in the construction industry, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    By Linda Arxis. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Occupational Summary: Carpentry, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: Building America, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: Accelerated Training in Apprentice Training Programs, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: Letter to J.W. Cisco re. Equal Opportunity Employment, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    By Hubert Beatty. Item is in English.
- Box: 15, Folder: 5 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Letter to Members, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    By A.J. Allen. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Indianapolis Plan - Open Shop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Box: 15, Folder: 6 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Report on Pension Plans Now in Force in MA, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Fundamentals of Employer-Employee Relations, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Box: 15, Folder: 7 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Simplified Evaluation Plan for Manual Type Jobs, Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Box: 15, Folder: 8 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Labor Department Guidelines on Noise, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Meeting Announcement, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Meeting Announcement, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: OSHA Bulletin, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Bulletin to Members re Minority Affairs, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Legal Counsel, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: AIC Spotlight, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: AIC Spotlight, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: AIC Spotlight, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Bulletin to Members re Holiday Doings, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Bulletin to Members re Snow Storms and Pay Practices, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Recent NLRB Results - Northeast Ohio Area, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: Effective Reduction of Absenteeism, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: AIC Spotlight, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: AIC Spotlight, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: AIC Spotlight, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: Bulletin to Members Erratum, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: AIC Spotlight, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 19: AIC Spotlight, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 20: Recent NLRB Results - Northeast Ohio Area, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 21: AIC Spotlight, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 22: AIC Spotlight, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 23: A Guide to Planning a Plant Tour, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 24: Speak up, Cleveland!, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 25: Union Membership, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 26: Employee Benefit Questionnaire, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 27: An Industrial Survey, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Box: 15, Folder: 9 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Management-Labor Relations Handbook, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Management-Labor Relations Handbook, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Management-Labor Relations Handbook, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Box: 15, Folder: 10 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A Brief Statement of Why Every Manufacturer, Merchant and Employer should be a Member, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: The Monitor; Vol. 8 No. 8, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Seventh Annual Get-Together Meeting and Dinner, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: State-wide Apprentice Training Program for Metal Trades, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Box: 15, Folder: 11 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Crisis or Common Sense, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Information Letter, No. 2125-2269, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Statement before the Interstate Commerce Commission ex parte no. 293 Northeastern Railroad Investigation, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Analysis of Surface Transportation Act, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Railroad Quiz, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Railroad Facts, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Education: AAR'S Success Story, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Railroad Review and Outlook, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: AAR, Its Organization and Activities, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Safety Section, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: Railroads in the Cost Spiral, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: Background Material for States, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 13: Statement before Subcomt. On Transportation and Commerce of the House Comt. On Interstate and Foreign Commerce, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    By Richard E. Briggs. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Annual Report, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 15: Letter to College Professors re. Transportation, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    By Anne O. Bennof. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Case for Competitive Equity, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 17: Coal and The Railroads, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 18: Why rails lack investor confidence, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    By Isabel H. Benham. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Piggybacking Takes Off, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 20: Topics; Vol. 10 No. 7, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 21: Executive Summary, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    By Union Pacific Railroad Co. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Traffic World, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 23: Government Expenditures, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 24: Textbooks on Railroads, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 25: Railroads of America, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 26: The Way to Better Rail Transportation, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    By R.V. Fletcher. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Railroad Transportation: A Statistical Record 1911-1947, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 28: Yearbook of Railroad Facts, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 29: Railroad Finance, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 30: Railroads in this Century, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 31: Railroad Personnel Practices, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 32: AAR, Its Organization and Activities, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 33: Railroad Facts, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 34: Railroad Facts, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 35: Railroad Facts, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Box: 15, Folder: 12 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Economic and Transportation Prospects, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: How should railroad freight rates be made?, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: A Check List of Railway Literature for Adults, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: You and Your Railroads, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: A Review of Railway Operations in 1946, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Interesting Facts about the American Railroads, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: The St. Lawrence Project, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Highway RobberyAgain?, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: Federal Expenditures for Highway, Waterway and Air Transportation Facilities, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: The Railroad World, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: News Flyer, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: Background on Transportation, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: Piggybacking Revenue Carloadings 1955-1965, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 14: Modern Railroads; Vol. 5 No. 6, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Box: 17, Folder: 1 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Women in Banking, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Box: 17, Folder: 2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: What ACME Is, Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: How to Get the Best Results from Management Consultants, Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
    By Philip W. Shay. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Directory of Membership and Services, Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Directory of Membership and Services, Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: What ACME Is, Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)